thanks for coming to my talk
谢谢你来我的演讲
services with spring cloud security I'm
我的Spring Cloud Security服务
will Tran
会陈
and please follow me on Twitter I do not
请在Twitter上关注我，我不
have many followers 510 will a little
有很多追随者510会一点
bit about me I'm spring user and I have
关于我的一点我是春季用户，我有
been since spring to dotto pretty much
从春天开始
my first job after University was re
我大学毕业后的第一份工作是
architecting at PHP application in
在PHP应用程序中进行架构设计
spring and I've been using spring ever
春天，我一直在用春天
attempts and through many strokes of
尝试并经过许多
luck I now work for pivotal actually
运气我现在为枢纽工作
because I've been working with a lot of
因为我一直在与很多
amazing people throughout my career I'm
我整个职业生涯中的杰出人物
now working for people I'm currently
现在为我目前所在的人工作
with the spring cloud services team if
与Spring Cloud Services团队合作
you follow the cloud native track you'll
您遵循云原生轨道
see a lot of what's been happening there
看到那里发生了很多事
and formerly I've been with pinnacle
以前我去过顶峰
single sign-on which is product built on
基于产品的单点登录
top of Cloud Foundry you aa4 a pitiful
Cloud Foundry的顶部，您可怜
Cloud Foundry I've also made a lot of
Cloud Foundry我也做了很多
commits to Cloud Foundry you AAA to make
承诺向Cloud Foundry提供AAA认证
it multi-tenant and before that I was
多租户，在那之前我是
working for pivotal Cloud Foundry mobile
为关键的Cloud Foundry移动工作
services this is my second time speaking
服务这是我第二次说话
at spring 1/2 GX you might have seen me
在GX春季1/2，您可能已经见过我
last year talking about as horn in
去年谈论作为号角
spring boot and I'm based in Toronto
spring boot ，我在多伦多工作
Canada so I guess I have to go over what
加拿大，所以我想我必须回顾一下
microservices are but I'm sure you've
微服务是，但我相信你已经
heard this repeated many times this
听到这个重复了很多遍
quotes from Adrian Cockroft formerly of
以前来自Adrian Cockroft的报价
Netflix and he describes them as a
Netflix，他形容他们是
loosely coupled service-oriented
松散耦合的面向服务
architecture with bounded context what
具有有限上下文的架构
he means by loosely coupled is that
他的意思是说，松散耦合是
services can be updated independently
服务可以独立更新
and what he means by boundary contacts
以及他所说的边界接触
are is that services are responsible for
是服务负责
a well-defined business function and
定义明确的业务职能，以及
care little about the services that
不在乎服务
surround it so I read that as do one
包围它，所以我读到就像一个
thing and do it well now in practice
事情，现在在实践中做好
micro service architectures are usually
微服务架构通常是
taste or they communicate via some other
品尝或通过其他方式交流
open standard there containerized they
开放标准在那里集装箱化
are independently deployable and
可独立部署
scalable and they are self-sufficient
可扩展且自给自足
which means that it makes as little
这意味着它几乎没有
assumptions as possible on the external
外部假设
Armin's so when you move to
阿明就是这样，当您搬到
microservices how does that affect
微服务如何影响
security first we'll go over a typical
安全第一，我们将介绍典型的
security setup for securing a monolith
用于保护整体的安全设置
you've got an HTTP request or HTTP
您有一个HTTP请求或HTTP
request coming in I hope everything is
请求进来，我希望一切都顺利
going over HTTP hits your load balancer
通过HTTP会影响您的负载均衡器
now your load balancer may or may not
现在您的负载均衡器可能会也可能不会
terminate the SSL connection maybe it's
终止SSL连接，也许是
starting a new SSL connection with the
使用以下命令启动新的SSL连接
app servers maybe the connection between
应用服务器之间的连接
the load balancer in your app servers
应用服务器中的负载均衡器
just HTTP but you're inside your your
只是HTTP，但您在自己的内部
network so that's fine
网络，这样很好
cool so request hits your app server you
很酷，因此请求会命中您的应用服务器
probably have an authentication layer
可能有一个认证层
built into the application the request
内置到应用程序中的请求
is authenticated and authorized and then
经过身份验证和授权，然后
the request gets passed along to various
该请求被传递给各种
modules in your application and you're
您的应用程序中的模块
probably sharing a single database
可能共享一个数据库
connection pool with a single set of
一组连接池
credentials to access the database that
访问数据库的凭据
hosts all of the data functionality of
托管的所有数据功能
your of your components so this is this
您的组件，所以这是这个
is easier than securing microservices
比保护微服务更容易
because you only need to authenticate
因为您只需要验证
the request once per request so if you
每个请求一次，因此，如果您
don't have a session you have to log in
没有会话，您必须登录
verify user credentials get the users
验证用户凭据获取用户
roles and start the user session if you
角色并启动用户会话（如果您
do have a session then you just have to
做一个会议，那么你只需要
verify that that session is not expired
验证该会话未过期
but that authentication layer takes care
但是该身份验证层需要注意
of all that for you and and then pass
所有这些对你来说，然后通过
that authentication layer your request
身份验证层您的请求
in a response the entire user request
在响应中，整个用户请求
and response is handled in process so
并在处理过程中响应
you can trust the method in Vacations
您可以信任Vacations中的方法
that your code is making with each other
您的代码正在相互影响
I hope you can trust it or else you're
我希望你可以相信它，否则你会
really paranoid so the pros to this is
真的很偏执，所以这个的优点是
that you have a limited attack service
您的攻击服务有限
there's really only one way in and out
实际上只有一种进出方式
of your application and that's easy to
您的应用程序，这很容易
control and manage but the cons here is
控制和管理，但这里的缺点是
that the application has all the
该应用程序具有所有
credentials it needs to do anything it
需要做任何事情的凭证
wants to the database if you can break
想进入数据库，如果可以中断
into that process then you get it all
进入那个过程，那么你就全部掌握了
so let's look at microservice
让我们来看一下微服务
architecture a little such as this where
这样的建筑有点
you've got your functionality broken up
您已经分解了功能
into each its own application each
进入每个自己的应用程序
application is accessing a database
应用程序正在访问数据库
using credentials that are specific for
使用专用于
that function that's kind of good
那种功能很好
because you can lament the principle of
因为你可以感叹
least privilege pretty well with this
最小特权与此很好
every component only has access to what
每个组件只能访问
it needs to perform its function but
它需要执行其功能，但
this is hard because you have a much
这很难，因为你有很多
larger attack service especially for
更大的攻击服务，尤其是针对
internal threats so there's a lot of
内部威胁，所以有很多
ways if you can get inside that Network
您能否进入该网络的方法
there's a lot of ways that you can mess
有很多方法可以弄乱
around and also how do you know how do
周围，​​你又怎么知道
other services know who is accessing
其他服务知道谁正在访问
them and how can other services trust
他们以及其他服务如何信任
each other so we'll talk about the this
彼此，所以我们将谈论这个
level set up here where you have a
在这里设置水平
request coming in hits your load
请求进来打你的负担
balancer hits an authentication
平衡器命中认证
authorization gateway so you have an
授权网关，这样您就可以
application whose only purpose is to
唯一目的是
authenticate and authorize the request
认证和授权请求
maybe it has a connection to a user
也许它与用户有联系
store once the request is checked then
一旦请求被存储，然后存储
it'll send a request to whatever service
它将向任何服务发送请求
it needs to go to and you can see here
它需要去，你可以在这里看到
that each of these services do not have
这些服务中的每一个都没有
an authentication layer at all okay so
身份验证层完全可以
with this sort of setup
通过这种设置
it's called API gateway or primary
它称为API网关或主要
parameters security and the public load
参数安全与公共负载
balancer can't send requests to apps
平衡器无法将请求发送到应用
directly let's go back here the network
直接让我们回到网络
setup only allows this load balancer to
安装程序仅允许此负载均衡器执行以下操作：
stand request the Gateway and then with
站请求网关，然后与
such a setup each of these apps can
每个应用程序都可以进行这样的设置
trust that ok the request has been
相信请求已经确定
authenticated and authorized by the
经认证和授权
Gateway so they trust all the traffic
网关，因此他们信任所有流量
they received by Assumption pros with
他们被假设专业人士接受
this is that network setup can virtually
这是网络设置实际上可以
guarantee these assumptions and apps
保证这些假设和应用
have stay
留下来
less security its stateless because
较少的安全其无状态，因为
they're just assuming that everything's
他们只是假设一切都在
secure so there's no other state may
安全，因此没有其他状态
there's just one there's just one state
只有一种只有一种状态
well the cons with this is that nothing
不好的是，这没什么
for internal threats if you can get into
如果您可以进入内部威胁
the network you can access any
您可以访问的网络
application you want so what if you
您想要的应用程序，如果您
built a security layer into every single
在每个人中建立一个安全层
app so one one approach with this is
应用程序，因此一种方法是
that you just use HTTP basic all apps
您只使用HTTP基本所有应用程序
get to do authentication authorization
做认证授权
themselves and basic credentials get
自己和基本凭证得到
passed along with every single request
与每个请求一起传递
the pros here is that it's stateless
这里的优点是它是无状态的
because you're authenticating the
因为您正在验证
request every single time you don't have
每次都没有时要求
to maintain the session and it's easy
保持会议，这很容易
because it should be basic support is
因为它应该是基本的支持
like free out-of-the-box but the cons
像免费的开箱即用，但缺点
here is that well how do you store and
这就是您如何存储和
look up user credentials and how do you
查找用户凭据以及如何
manage authorization also you have user
也有用户管理授权
credentials being passed around all over
凭证到处传递
the network and fene gets handle on
网络和友谊得到处理
those user financials you can unlock all
这些用户财务状况，您可以解锁所有
the functionality that that user can
该用户可以使用的功能
perform forever until the user updates
永远执行直到用户更新
their password any questions so far okay
到目前为止，他们的密码有任何问题都可以
look keep going all right so what if we
看起来一切顺利，如果我们
kept all that same stuff but used a
保留所有相同的东西，但使用了
centralized authentication store or
集中认证存储或
maybe it's just a sequel database or
也许只是续集数据库，或者
something like that so we still have
这样的事情，所以我们仍然有
basic auth all the apps get to do
所有应用程序要做的基本身份验证
authentication authorization themselves
认证授权本身
credentials are verified against the
凭证根据
central DB and this is good because you
中央数据库，这很好，因为您
have a central user store one source of
有一个中央用户存储一个来源
truth and it's still stateless but then
事实，它仍然是无状态的，但是
a year off DB gets hit every real
一年的DB遭受打击
question that could be a bottleneck and
问题可能是瓶颈，
now your look up logic has to be
现在您的查找逻辑必须是
implemented everywhere same deal with
在所有地方都实施相同的处理
user credentials they're being passed
被传递的用户凭证
around all over the place and it can
到处都是，它可以
hold locked
保持锁定
all functionality okay so what if we use
所有功能都很好，如果我们使用
sessions keep all that same stuff but
会议保持所有相同的东西，但
each app gets to maintain a session with
每个应用都可以与之保持会话
a client device that alleviates the off
缓解关闭的客户端设备
DB as being a bottleneck because that DB
数据库成为瓶颈，因为该数据库
is only hit once per session but it's
每个会话仅被击中一次，但是
hard to manage all the sessions you have
很难管理所有的会议
a separate session with every
每个人都有一个单独的会话
application you don't get single sign-on
您没有单点登录的应用程序
you still have dbl look up logic that
您仍然有dbl查找逻辑，
has to be implemented everywhere and you
必须在任何地方实施，您
still have user credentials being passed
仍然有用户凭证通过
all over the place okay how about API
到处都可以，API怎么样
tokens so forget about all the HTTP
令牌，所以忘记所有HTTP
basic stuff and instead you have a
基本的东西，相反，你有一个
username and password that gets
用户名和密码
exchanged for a token at a central
在中央交换令牌
authorization server ops can get this
授权服务器操作可以获取此信息
token the request and then validate the
标记请求，然后验证
token by making a call back to the
通过回拨令牌来
authorization server and the pros here
授权服务器和专业人士在这里
is that the apps never see the user
是应用程序永远不会看到用户
financials the only thing that sees user
财务唯一看到用户的东西
credentials is the authorization server
凭据是授权服务器
that gets user credentials and exchanges
获得用户凭证和交换
them for a token but the cons here is
他们为令牌，但这里的缺点是
that the authorization server becomes
授权服务器成为
the bottleneck because every request
瓶颈，因为每个请求
results every request that a micro
结果每一个微请求
Service receives results in another
服务在另一个接收结果
request to the auth server to validate
请求验证服务器进行验证
the token and if you're just rolling
令牌，如果您只是滚动
your own API token layer you might not
您自己的API令牌层，您可能不会
be building in an authorization
建立授权
component so tokens provide nothing
组件，因此令牌不提供任何内容
access sort of the same thing with user
与用户访问类似的东西
credentials
证书
okay how about sam'l sam'l is good it's
好的，萨姆尔萨姆尔很好
standard in sam'l an identity provider
身份提供商中的标准
provides sign decisions to apps
为应用提供签名决定
so what a signed assertion is is that
所以签名的断言是
it's basically sets of keys and values
它基本上是键和值的集合
but you can but it's signed so you can
但您可以但已签名，因此您可以
verify that this information came from a
验证此信息来自
trusted source and apps can trust these
受信任的来源和应用程序可以信任这些
assertions and verify them themselves
断言并自己验证
and the pros here is that you have a
这里的优点是你有一个
standard trust model but the cons is
标准信任模型，但缺点是
that samwell's xml-based
samwell基于xml的
xml is big and stinking scary for a lot
xml很大，而且让很多人感到恐惧
of developers and it's also difficult
开发人员，这也很困难
for non browser clients to participate
非浏览器客户参与
in sam'l there is a sam'l to profile
在sam'l中有一个sam'l
called ECP but I don't think it's very
叫做ECP，但我认为这不是非常
well supported so I've brought up a lot
很好的支持，所以我提出了很多
of common concerns here there's the
共同关心的是
bottleneck of a central user store
中央用户商店的瓶颈
you'll want to have single sign-on of
您需要单次登录
course you want to keep things as
当然你想保留东西
stateless as possible especially your
尽可能无国籍，尤其是你
your back-end services once you get user
获得用户后您的后端服务
credentials game over you'll probably
您的凭证游戏可能会
want fine-grained authorization and you
需要细粒度的授权，您
want interoperability with non browser
希望与非浏览器互操作
clients so enter to an open ID connect
客户，因此输入一个开放的ID连接
what's oauth2 it's a delegated
什么是oauth2，这是委派的
authorization protocol it's a protocol
授权协议这是一个协议
for conveying authorization decisions
用于传达授权决定
via token and it's standard means of
通过令牌，这是
obtaining a token via the for off to
通过for来获取令牌
grant types for grant types or
授予类型或授予类型
authorization code and you'll use this
授权码，您将使用它
if you have a web application and it's
如果您有一个Web应用程序，
also the most secure grant type which
也是最安全的授权类型
and you'll see why in a little bit we
然后您会明白为什么
also have the resource owner password
也有资源所有者密码
grant so you can use this if you have a
授予，以便您可以在有
web application but let's say you want
Web应用程序，但假设您要
to host your own login page instead of
托管自己的登录页面，而不是
using the login page on the
使用登录页面上的
authorization server or let's say you
授权服务器，或者说您
are some non browser clients and you
是一些非浏览器客户端，您
want to participate no off - here's the
不想参加-这是
implicit grant the implicit grant is
隐式授予隐式授予是
used if you have a single page
如果您只有一页，则使用
JavaScript app so it is browser specific
JavaScript应用程序，因此它是特定于浏览器的
but it's if you have a single page
但是如果你只有一页
JavaScript app and really no back-end
JavaScript应用程序，实际上没有后端
and the client credentials grant is used
和客户端凭据授予被使用
when a client or a machine is operating
当客户端或机器正在运行时
by itself so it's not operating on
本身，所以它不会在
behalf of the user
代表用户
so for back-end processes that might
因此对于可能
happen asynchronously that's that can be
异步发生就是这样
so you have these four grant types that
所以你有这四种补助类型
cover pretty much every situation that
涵盖了几乎所有情况
you could think of and with oauth2
您可以想到并使用oauth2
users and clients are separate entities
用户和客户端是独立的实体
which allows you to say something like I
这样你就可以说像我
am authorizing this app to form these
正在授权此应用来形成这些
actions on my behalf but o2 is not
代表我采取行动，但o2不是
authentication it says nothing about how
身份验证它没有说明如何
the user is authenticated it does say
用户通过身份验证时会说
that in order to obtain a token the user
为了获得令牌的用户
must be authenticated but it also
必须经过认证，但同时
doesn't say how a token is validated nor
没有说令牌是如何验证的
does it say what a tokens supposed to
它说令牌应该做什么
look like or if it's supposed to contain
看起来还是应该包含
any information you can read more about
您可以阅读更多有关的任何信息
this and Olaf net so that in what is
这个和奥拉夫网，所以在什么
open ID Connect well open ID Connect is
打开ID Connect好打开ID Connect是
a delegated authentication protocol
委托认证协议
built on top of OAuth 2 and in this
建立在OAuth 2之上
protocol user identity is conveyed via
协议用户身份通过
signs JWT which stands for JSON web
签署代表JSON Web的JWT
token and in short you can just call it
令牌，总之您可以调用它
jot it provides a standard needs for
记下它为
obtaining an ID token and you can do
获取ID令牌，您可以
that over the same for oauth2 grant
对于oauth2授予​​相同
types and there's also a standard means
类型，还有一种标准的方法
of verifying ID tokens so that's a
验证ID令牌的过程
little bit of an extra thing that you're
你有点多余的东西
getting in the open ID connect
进入开放ID连接
specification and it allows you to say
规范，它允许您说
things like will is authorizing this app
诸如will之类的事情正在授权该应用
to perform actions on his behalf so
代表他执行动作
these tokens convey both authorization
这些令牌传达了两种授权
and I did and identity and you can also
我做到了，身份也可以
if an application needs to see this
如果应用程序需要查看此内容
person's email address there's a
人的电子邮件地址中有一个
standard way of conveying claims about
传达有关以下内容的标准方式
one's identity email address phone
一个人的身份电子邮件地址电话
number mailing address all sorts of
各种邮寄地址
stuff like that
像那样的东西
open ID connect is not ossification
开放ID连接不是骨化
though it still doesn't say how users
虽然它仍然没有说用户如何
are to be authenticated but this is a
要进行身份验证，但这是一个
good thing because there's a lot of ways
好东西，因为有很多方法
to authenticate users you can roll your
要验证用户身份，您可以滚动
own internal database you can hook it up
自己的内部数据库，您可以将其连接
to another identity provider over sam'l
通过sam'转到另一个身份提供者
or LDAP you can do things like
或LDAP，您可以执行以下操作
multi-factor authentication all of that
多因素身份验证
is possible and open ID Connect but not
可以并打开ID Connect，但不能
really specified by the spec do you have
规格确实指定了吗
any questions so far no ok so I'm going
到目前为止有任何问题，不好，我要去
to walk through the authorization codes
浏览授权码
flow I know there's four different ones
流程我知道有四个不同的流程
but this is the one that you'll probably
但这是你可能会遇到的那个
see the most often it's also the most
看到最多，也是最多
complicated but it is the most secure so
复杂，但这是最安全的
in this little example we've got these
在这个小例子中，我们有这些
four actors user and in both speak it's
四个演员用户，两者都说
the resource owner the web app here and
资源所有者此处的Web应用程序，以及
a lot to speak is the client the REST
很多话是客户端REST
API over here is also called the
这里的API也称为
resource server and the authorization
资源服务器和授权
server and Oban ID Connect speak is
服务器和Oban ID Connect说话是
called the Open ID connect provider so
称为开放ID连接提供者，因此
you'll see these sort of ladder terms
您会看到这些阶梯术语
used a lot in documentation and the
在文档中使用了很多
setup here is that sort of the situation
这里的设置就是这种情况
before I begin is that no the user has
在我开始之前，没有用户
no session with the authorization server
没有与授权服务器的会话
or the web app and the use case that I'm
或我所使用的网络应用和用例
going to demonstrate is the user wants
要演示是用户想要的
to place an order on the REST API using
使用以下命令在REST API上下订单
the web app so step one user accesses
网络应用程序，因此第一步用户可以访问
the web app and does not have the
网络应用程序，并且没有
session with it so the web app says note
会话，因此网络应用会显示“注意”
you're not authenticated and it's going
您未通过身份验证，并且要进行
to redirect the user to the authorized
将用户重定向到授权
endpoint on the auth server the redirect
身份验证服务器上的端点重定向
URL contains the scopes open ID and
URL包含范围的开放ID和
order dot me scopes are like permissions
命令点我的范围就像权限
or roles and when these scopes end up in
或角色以及这些范围何时结束
a token that token says this user can do
令牌表明该用户可以执行的令牌
these particular things
这些特别的事情
okay so the auth server gets a request
好的，因此身份验证服务器会收到请求
to authorize end point but then
授权终点，但随后
redirects the user back to its login
将用户重定向回其登录名
page because the users are not logged in
页面，因为用户未登录
so the user logs in and starts a session
因此用户登录并开始会话
with the authorization server and now is
与授权服务器，现在是
redirected back to the authorized
重定向回授权
endpoint the authorization server
终结点授权服务器
remember what the user was trying to do
记住用户正在尝试做什么
in the first place before they had to
首先，他们不得不
login so now you see a page and you
登录，所以现在您看到一个页面，您
probably see in this page a lot where
可能在此页面上看到很多地方
you have to authorize the web app to do
您必须授权网络应用才能执行
things on on their behalf so the user
事物代表他们，所以用户
sees a page and the page asks easier to
看到一个页面，页面问起来更容易
permit the web app to access their
允许网络应用访问其
identity and manage their orders on
识别并管理他们的订单
their behalf so the user says yep that's
他们代表，所以用户说是
good and hit submit and the user
好，点击提交和用户
authorizes access so the authorization
授权访问，因此授权
server redirects the user back to the
服务器将用户重定向回
web app with a one time code and the
具有一次性代码和
query parameters of the redirect the web
网页重定向查询参数
app receives this one time code and so
应用收到此一次性代码，因此
I'm showing this dotted line here the
我在这里显示这条虚线
user is sort of waiting on a response
用户有点等待响应
but the web app is doing some stuff in
但网络应用程序正在做一些事情
the background the web app receives the
网络应用收到的背景
one time coach and the query parameters
一次教练和查询参数
and then goes to hit the authorization
然后去打授权
server with this one time code in the
与此时间代码中的服务器
back and and the officer v validates the
返回，然后警官v验证
code because it just generated it so now
代码，因为它现在才生成它
the off server returns responds back to
离机服务器返回响应
the web server it responds with an
响应的Web服务器
access token
访问令牌
which could look like a random string
看起来像是随机字符串
and an ID token which is assigned JWT
和分配给JWT的ID令牌
and so I'll go over what a JWT look like
因此，我将介绍一下JWT的外观
looks like in the demo so now the web
看起来像在演示中，所以现在网络
app can verify the ID token consume its
应用可以验证ID令牌是否消耗了其
contents and start an authenticated
内容并开始验证
session and it saves the access token in
会话，并将访问令牌保存在
session so now the user is authenticated
会话，因此现在用户已通过身份验证
with the auth server users authenticated
与认证服务器用户进行身份验证
with the web app
使用网络应用
webapp now gives control back to the
webapp现在将控制权交还给
user and responds with an order form and
用户并以订单形式答复
now I'm going to go over now that the
现在我要过去了
users all signed in how this affects the
所有用户都登录了，这如何影响
resource server room back here
资源服务器机房回到这里
authorization code flow is finished but
授权码流程已完成，但
user still needs to actually do
用户仍然需要实际执行
something on this application so the
在这个应用程序上的东西，所以
user fills out and submits an order form
用户填写并提交订单
and the webapp submits the order to the
然后网络应用将订单提交给
REST API using the access token that was
使用访问令牌的REST API
stored in session remember when the
存储在会话中时记得
authorization server responded the web
授权服务器响应了网络
app starts an authenticated session and
应用程序启动经过身份验证的会话，
saves the access token in that session
在该会话中保存访问令牌
and that add that access token is
并且添加该访问令牌是
present in the request to the REST API
存在于对REST API的请求中
in an authorization header so the REST
在授权标头中，因此REST
API needs to validate this token it
API需要验证此令牌
sends the token back to the
将令牌发送回
authorization service token verification
授权服务令牌验证
endpoint all services yep token is okay
终结点所有服务都可以令牌
and these are the permissions that token
这些是令牌的权限
grants so the REST API can see that okay
授予，以便REST API可以看到
this request is authorized to to manage
该请求被授权管理
orders but now the REST API before
订购，但现在使用REST API
saving the order wants to get more
保存订单要获得更多
information about the user let's say it
说说有关用户的信息
needs to get the user's address or phone
需要获取用户的地址或电话
number and this information is not in
号，此信息不在
the request from the web app so it can
来自网络应用的请求，因此它可以
make another request to the
再次向
authorization server using the same
授权服务器使用相同的
token it's making a request to the user
令牌向用户发出请求
info endpoint the user info endpoint is
信息端点用户信息端点是
a standard endpoint in open ID Connect
开放ID Connect中的标准端点
and the response is is user information
响应是用户信息
essentially suddenly the off server
基本上突然关闭服务器
responds with that information and now
响应该信息，现在
the REST API can save the order it's
REST API可以保存订单
filled it all filled in all the fields
填满所有领域
and finally control is now given back to
最后，控制权现在交还给
the user so that's how a resource server
用户，这就是资源服务器的方式
consumes the token now how about single
现在消耗令牌
sign-on let's say there's another web
假设有另一个网站
app and the user wants use web app to to
应用，并且用户希望使用Web应用来
track their order
跟踪他们的订单
the users not authenticated with it so
用户未通过身份验证
this is kind of the same thing the web
这在网络上是一样的
app redirects the user back to the
应用将用户重定向回
office servers authorized endpoint but
办公服务器授权端点，但
the user is already authenticated with
用户已经通过身份验证
this guy sessions still alive so the
这个家伙会议仍然活着，所以
user so the authorization server
用户，因此授权服务器
responds to the authorized request with
响应授权请求
another page that asks if the user
另一个页面询问用户
permits the web app to access their
允许网络应用访问其
identity and manage orders on their
识别并管理他们的订单
behalf and the flow continues so that's
代表，流程继续，所以
a lot of hopscotch and that's why we
很多跳房子，这就是为什么我们
have spring cloud security so with
具有spring-cloud-security性，因此
spring cloud security you get single
spring-cloud-security单身
sign-on with OAuth 2 and Open ID Connect
使用OAuth 2和Open ID Connect登录
servers and you can achieve this with a
服务器，您可以使用
single annotation and some configuration
单个注释和一些配置
you can also secure resource servers
您还可以保护资源服务器
with tokens also with a single
与令牌也与单个
annotation and some config and it also
注释和一些配置，它也
gives you the ability to relay your
使您能够中继您的
tokens between single sign-on enabled
启用单点登录之间的令牌
web apps and resource servers and it
Web应用程序和资源服务器及其
gives you this with an auto configure to
通过自动配置为您提供
off to rest template so this whole
休息模板，这样整个
situation here it lets you do this all
这种情况可以让您完成所有操作
very easily there is a caveat though
很容易有一个警告
that I mean open ID connect it just
我的意思是打开ID连接它
became a standard recently and because
最近成为标准，因为
of that spring cloud security or spring
春天的安全性或春天
security OAuth 2 actually doesn't
安全性OAuth 2实际上没有
consume the Open ID Connect tokens
消耗Open ID Connect令牌
directly what it does support those that
它直接支持那些
it does support the user info endpoint
它确实支持用户信息端点
so if your application needs to get
因此，如果您的应用程序需要获取
identity information get more identity
身份信息获得更多身份
information it can do that through the
信息可以通过
user info endpoint but it's not going to
用户信息端点，但不会
use the ID token yet however if an
使用ID令牌，但是如果
access token is JWT containing identity
访问令牌是包含身份的JWT
claims then it can consume all that all
声称它可以消耗所有
in one shot
一枪
but didn't I say access tickets where
但是我不是说在哪里买票
we'll pick well this is what the ohe
我们会选择好的，这就是
spec says access tokens are credentials
规范说访问令牌是凭证
used to access protected resources and
用于访问受保护的资源，以及
access token is a string representing an
访问令牌是代表
authorization issued to the client the
授权给客户
string is usually opaque to the client
字符串通常对客户端不透明
so they're suggesting that the string
所以他们建议字符串
can just be some random gibberish now
现在可能只是一些乱码
the client doesn't understand but it's
客户不明白，但是
not saying that the string must in big
并不是说字符串必须很大
all caps letters be opaque to the client
所有大写字母对客户都是不透明的
so really we're free to make that string
所以实际上我们可以自由地制作那根弦
whatever we want so if access tokens
无论我们想要什么，如果访问令牌
carried information then with scopes in
然后携带范围内的信息
the token you can authorize the request
您可以授权请求的令牌
yourselves yourself and with identity
自我和身份
claims in the token you can know who the
在令牌中声明您可以知道谁
originator of that request is and if
该请求的发起者是，如果
that token is signs then you can
该令牌是标志，那么你可以
validate the tokens authentic assent
验证令牌的真实同意
isset e yourself you don't have to pass
让自己烦恼，您不必通过
that off token back to the off server to
将关闭令牌返回到关闭服务器
validate it and get a response you can
验证并获得您可以的回应
do it all yourself so your auth server
自己完成所有操作，以便您的身份验证服务器
won't become a bottleneck questions cool
不会成为瓶颈问题
so how do we get all this enter you AAA
那么我们如何获得所有这些进入AAA
what is you AAA you a is the user
您是什么AAA您是用户
account and authorization server and
帐户和授权服务器以及
it's a core component of Cloud Foundry
它是Cloud Foundry的核心组件
its Babel tested in production it's the
它的Babel在生产中经过测试
same server if you use run dot pivotal
如果您使用运行点关键的是同一台服务器
IO or people web services it's it's
IO或人员Web服务
running there as well it runs with every
在那里也可以运行
cloud factory deployment in fact it's
云工厂部署实际上是
Apache 2 license so you can download the
Apache 2许可证，因此您可以下载
war and run it for free you can see all
战争并免费运行它，您可以看到所有
the source code on github.com slash
github.com上的源代码斜杠
Cloud Foundry slash you AAA
Cloud Foundry大幅降低您AAA
it's very actively developed as well
它也非常活跃
it's a lot too compliant and it's almost
这太合规了，几乎
open ID Connect compliance full
完全符合ID Connect要求
compliance I'm sure will be happening
我敢肯定会遵守
very soon I know that they're working on
很快我知道他们正在努力
on a couple issues right now but it does
现在有几个问题，但确实
support the user info endpoint it's also
支持用户信息端点
multi-tenant and spring security off to
多租户和春季安全保障
is actually based on UA UA came first
实际上是基于UA UA排在第一位
and then allow that code was pulled out
然后允许该代码被拔出
and then spring security OAuth 2 was
然后春季安全OAuth 2是
created from that and spring cloud
从那和春天的云创建
security which is basically spring boot
安全基本上是 spring boot
plus spring security OAuth 2 is a great
加上Spring Security OAuth 2很棒
fit with UI a because you a produces a
适合UI a，因为您会产生一个
jot containing both scopes at identity
记下两个作用域的身份
in the access token so all of this talk
在访问令牌中，所以所有这些讨论
about jaw what is it John stands for
关于下巴约翰代表什么
JSON web token it was standardized well
JSON Web令牌，它标准化良好
it became proposed standard May 2015 a
它成为2015年5月提议的标准
jot consists of a header a payload and a
jot由标头，有效负载和
signature the header described how that
签名标题描述了如何
signature hello okay header describes
签名你好好头说明
how that signature was generated what
该签名是如何产生的
algorithm was used and provides a
使用了算法，并提供了
standard way of verifying that signature
验证签名的标准方法
jots when base64 encoded are very easy
进行base64编码时非常容易
to transmit in headers they can
传输标题，他们可以
encapsulate any claim so you can have
封装任何声明，以便您可以拥有
scopes identity stuff but all sorts of
范围标识的东西，但各种
other information anything that you
其他信息，任何你
really you can throw into JSON you can
真的，您可以将其放入JSON中
encapsulate in the Jade
封装在翡翠中
in the jot payload they have expiry and
在Jot有效载荷中，它们已经到期并且
with all this you can have scalable
有了这些，您就可以扩展
stateless authentication and
无状态验证和
authorization clients can verify tokens
授权客户端可以验证令牌
themselves but there is a trade-off
本身，但需要权衡
because you lose out on token
因为你输了令牌
replication so if you're not making a
复制，因此，如果您不进行
call back to an authorization server
回调到授权服务器
then really you just have to rely on the
那么实际上您只需要依靠
tokens expiry to know if that user still
令牌到期以了解该用户是否仍然
or that client is still a lot to do
还是那个客户还有很多事要做
whatever they're doing and this should
他们在做什么，这应该
solve the common concerns that I
解决我的共同担忧
mentioned previously where there's a
前面提到的那里有一个
bottleneck in the central user store
中央用户存储中的瓶颈
don't need it don't have that anymore
不需要它了
you can achieve single sign-on resource
您可以实现单点登录资源
servers can be stateless you're not
服务器可以是无状态的，而您不是
passing user credentials around all over
各地传递用户凭证
the place your tokens can contain
您的令牌可以包含的位置
fine-grained authorization and it's
细粒度的授权，它是
really easy for non browser clients to
非浏览器客户端真的很容易
enter up with with this okay so let's
进入这个好吧，让我们
see it all work if you want you can
如果您愿意，可以看到全部工作
follow along in these steps on github
在github上按照这些步骤进行操作
I'm going to try to display some of the
我将尝试显示一些
code on this screen but if it's hard to
屏幕上的代码，但如果很难
read then you may want to just go on to
阅读然后您可能想要继续
github and and look at the the repo here
github，然后在这里查看仓库
and everything's a master okay so the
一切都很好，所以
first demo here that I'll show you is
我将向您展示的第一个演示是
single sign-on and so I've set up an app
单一登录，所以我已经设置了一个应用
that can see can consume gules open ID
可以看到可以消耗红色打开的ID
connects endpoints and it can also
连接端点，它也可以
consume UA a with the only difference
消耗UA a的唯一区别
being configuration
正在配置
so I've deployed an application to PWS
所以我已经将应用程序部署到PWS
and
和
surely what hello okay this this link
当然，你好吗，这个链接
here is pretty will forward me to a
这很漂亮会将我转发给
sign-in page and so right now let's open
登录页面，所以现在让我们打开
ID Connect provider I'm going to sign in
我要登录的ID Connect供应商
cool now I've already authorized this
现在很酷，我已经授权了
application to access the credentials or
申请访问凭证或
access my genic
访问我的基因
what you are seeing here is theirs with
你在这里看到的是他们的
the access token that Google this token
Google使用此令牌的访问令牌
here it's pretty
这很漂亮
an ID connect provider
ID连接提供者
and I guess didn't track that okay so
而且我猜没有追踪到
but can you
但是你能
my audio is cutting in and out isn't it
我的音频切入切出不是吗
ah man in the back can you hear me
啊，后面的人你能听见我吗
alright I'll try to be loud yep
好吧，我会大声说
okay cool let's yeah let's go back here
好的，很酷，是的，让我们回到这里
do this
做这个
thanks Matt cool okay so yeah access
谢谢马特酷好，所以是的访问
token base64 it's pretty small here's
令牌base64，这很小
some info and now to switch off the
一些信息，现在要关闭
Google support and single sign-on with
Google支持和的单点登录
you eh eh so I know I'm talking about
你恩，所以我知道我在说
open source you eh eh this or pivotal
开源，无论是关键还是关键
Cloud Foundry it's pivotal single
Cloud Foundry这是关键
sign-on so I'm going to bind it to the
登录，以便将其绑定到
pivot single sign-on service start the
枢轴单点登录服务启动
app oh cool sound guy good is this
应用程序哦，酷，声音很好，这是这个
microphone issue gonna get worked up
麦克风问题会解决
great thank you all right looks like
很好，谢谢，看起来不错
we're live so I'm going to go back to
我们还活着，所以我要回去
this app again now I see a different
现在我再次看到这个应用程序
login page this login page is hosted on
登录页面托管在此登录页面上
PWS but it's a login page for my my
PWS，但这是我的登录页面
specific tenant of pivotal single
关键单身的特定租户
sign-on and it'll sign in here
登录，它将在这里登录
maybe it's oh right I forgot to do one
也许是哦，我忘了做一个
thing yeah I'm actually not set up on
是的，我实际上没有设置
the internal identity provider which is
内部身份提供者
just database so I'm going to hook this
只是数据库，所以我要钩上这个
guy up to a sam'l identity provider
由同一个人身份提供者负责
and you'd like to preview which is a
并且您想预览哪个是
saml environment we offer testing
我们提供测试的saml环境
what was my password
我的密码是多少
great and where's my phone so now the
太好了，我的手机在哪里，所以现在
cool thing that I'm showing you here is
我在这里向你展示的很酷的东西是
that if you hook up an open ID Connect
如果您连接了开放的ID Connect
provider to like a sam'l IDP then that
提供商喜欢萨姆IDP然后
sam'l IDP can enforce the multi-factor
相同的IDP可以强制执行多因素
authentication that's the thing
身份验证就是这样
okay so now we see an authorization page
好的，现在我们看到授权页面
do I allowed this application to access
我是否允许该应用程序访问
data so this is the user info I got from
数据，这是我从中获得的用户信息
the user info endpoint using this token
使用此令牌的用户信息端点
but it's jokin and I won't call it
但这是乔金，我不会叫它
okay so you can see here highlighted or
好的，所以您可以在此处看到突出显示的内容或
jot token and what the header looks like
记记令牌以及标头的外观
the body and the signature looks like
身体和签名看起来像
the delimited by its rhythm that was
由其节奏界定的
used to generate the signature r56 and
用于生成签名r56和
this is the payload you've got token ID
这是您拥有令牌ID的有效负载
subject ID so this is unique identifier
主题ID，所以这是唯一的标识符
the client ID that I used to get the
我用来获取
token that my username email so there's
令牌，我的用户名电子邮件，所以
identity information there as well this
那里的身份信息
is the time that the token was issued
是令牌发行的时间
and the children will expire and she
孩子们会过期，她
have audience claims in here as well
也有观众要求
this odd field here says that this token
这个奇数场在这里说这个令牌
is intended to be used for the open ID
旨在用于开放ID
connect endpoint and intended to be used
连接端点并打算使用
for this application which is the client
此应用程序是客户端
ID which is this application here so
这里是这个应用程序的ID
that's a jot token and you're probably
这是一个记号，你可能是
wondering okay this is cool how do I set
想知道这很酷我该如何设置
it set it up how do I use Springs out
它设置了我如何使用弹簧
cloud security to do this also on to my
云安全性也可以做到这一点
next demo
下一个演示
okay so my next topic here is called
好吧，所以我的下一个话题是
Freddy's barbecue joint
弗雷迪的烧烤店
the actors are Freddy who's the owner of
演员是弗雷迪（Freddy），他是
Freddy's barbecue joint which makes the
弗雷迪的烧烤接头使
best ribs in DC we have Frank who is
DC最好的肋骨，我们有Frank是谁
Freddy's most important customer because
弗雷迪最重要的客户，因为
he's the most powerful man in the world
他是世界上最有权势的人
and we have the developer who works for
我们有为之工作的开发人员
Frank and wants to press him with this
弗兰克，想以此来压迫他
side project and the use case here is to
副项目，这里的用例是
give Frank the ability to see the menu
使弗兰克能够查看菜单
online and place orders and to give
在线下订单并发出
Freddy the ability to manage the menu
弗雷迪管理菜单的能力
and close orders so we are going to
并关闭订单，所以我们要
build this we have worked late we're
建立这个我们已经工作很晚了
going to build two UI applications and
将要构建两个UI应用程序，
two REST API resource servers and these
两个REST API资源服务器，
are all the pathways that are going to
是所有的途径
be followed okay so first let's start
跟着好吧，所以首先开始
with setting up UA a if you want to
如果需要，可以设置UA
preview of all this stuff on github and
在github和
read along
一起阅读
I'm going to show you the code let me
我将向您展示代码让我
know what looks better it's more
知道看起来更好的东西
readable on the screen yes
在屏幕上可读
so what do you guys with it is or
所以你们用的是
looking at looking at it in this yes
看着这是的
these are going to get up yes
这些会起床的
forget help for us yes I'm saying okay
忘记为我们提供帮助是的，我要说的是
oh I'll stick with STS because it's
哦，我会坚持使用STS，因为它
actually kind of like when I start
其实有点像我开始的时候
changing code like I'm going to walk
像我要走路一样更改代码
through every single commitments about
通过每一个关于
30 minutes that I find a groom's very
30分钟我觉得新郎很
well to show you how to create the
好向您展示如何创建
pretty funky joint system I kind of like
我喜欢的非常时髦的关节系统
the side-by-side comparison let's go
并排比较让我们开始吧
okay
好的
so first we've got got a you a
所以首先我们有一个你
configuration file we're going to be
我们将成为的配置文件
running all of this locally so to
在本地运行所有这些，以便
configure your own local you a a I've
配置您自己的本地设备
got it here in the comments for this
在这里的评论中得到它
commit you can download you a a from
提交您可以从下载
even set just search for it or Cloud
甚至设置只是搜索它还是云
Foundry identity Cloud Foundry ID any
铸造厂身份Cloud Foundry ID任何
you a once you have it set the
你一次，一旦设置
environment variable you a config path
环境变量您的配置路径
to the folder that contains this you a
到包含此文件夹的文件夹中
amo so it's in the project folder you a
amo，所以它在您的项目文件夹中
and then you can run this war in your
然后你可以在你的战争中
favorite container but in this demo run
最喜欢的容器，但在此演示运行中
it as localhost 8080 slash you a a once
它作为localhost 8080一次砍你
you have that setup commit which I
你有我的设置提交
really go over it contains the SSO
真正超过它包含SSO
application that I just MOU let's go to
我刚要谅解的应用程序
the first commit doing some this commit
第一次提交执行此提交
now establishes the customer UI
现在建立客户界面
just
只是
okay so we're going to create the
好的，我们要创建
customer UI with no security
没有安全性的客户界面
let's look at the application
让我们看一下应用程序
yep it's pretty small we have that
是的，我们很小
spring beauty application this is also a
春季美容应用这也是
controller so I'm making this class both
控制器，所以我都上这堂课
a controller and in the application
控制器和应用程序中
because I'm lazy and I always want to
因为我很懒，我一直想
show everything and went file um I
显示一切，然后去文件我
cannot how do you sue an STS I don't
你怎么不起诉我
think I could ever do that
认为我可以做到
okay see if that will work
好吧，看看是否行得通
sorry oh yeah there we go
抱歉，哦，是的，我们走了
cool yes so we've got to request
不错，所以我们必须要求
mappings we've got a home page I'm using
我们有一个正在使用的主页映射
spring MVC with time leaf and it's just
春天的MVC与时间的叶子，这只是
going to return the index template just
将只返回索引模板
kind of stuff it the valley here throw
这里的山谷扔的东西
in the string will or click with the
在字符串中将或单击
actual authentication later and I'm also
稍后进行实际身份验证，我也
stubbing out the response from the menu
从菜单中找出响应
resource server right here I am going to
资源服务器就在这里
rich mate
有钱人
I won't really go over the HTML let's
我不会真正浏览HTML，让我们
look at the domain object here which is
看看这里的领域对象
out and what are the dependencies here
出来，这里有什么依赖性
just spring boots starter time leaf and
只是 spring boot 起步时间叶和
the common project that holds in the
包含在
common domain model all right let's run
通用域模型好吧，让我们运行
it that's a pretty running it is
这是一个很好的运行
okay I can it's saying hi will but
好吧，我可以说你好，但是
that's a hard-coded value see the menu
这是一个硬编码的值，请参阅菜单
and this is just some stub debt values
这只是一些存根债务值
so this establishes the basic functions
这样就建立了基本功能
of the customer app right now and we can
现在，我们可以
move on to the next commit yeah
继续下一个提交是的
basically a four gig JVM though I've
我基本上有一个四演出的JVM
heard about visible
听说可见
okay no problem thanks guys
好的，没问题，谢谢大家
it's all good okay so now we're going to
一切都很好，所以现在我们要
add single sign-on to the application
将单点登录添加到应用程序
inter main application class I've got
我的主要应用程序类别
this annotation unable off to SSO
此注释无法发送到SSO
I've also added this dump token endpoint
我还添加了此转储令牌端点
config this is another class that I
配置这是我的另一类
wrote in the common package so that's
写在通用包中，所以
just for debugging the token but we
仅用于调试令牌，但我们
don't really need to focus on this this
真的不需要专注于这个
is where all the magic happens when you
是当你所有魔法发生的地方
add it then bring in the request mapping
添加它，然后引入请求映射
problem okay let's keep going
问题好吧，让我们继续前进
you can pop well object a standard it's
你可以弹出一个标准的对象
part of the Java standard it just means
只是Java标准的一部分
the authentication and instead of
身份验证，而不是
hard-coding will I'm going to use the
硬编码我将要使用
principal cat name to show you that it's
主猫的名字告诉你
really getting a jetty D sign what did
真的得到了码头D标志
we change in our config properties
我们更改配置属性
spring to Ottawa to
春天到渥太华
and we need to tell the application
我们需要告诉应用程序
where to go to get a token where to
在哪里获得代币在哪里
redirect the user to y'all
将用户重定向到所有人
John you a a s20 the token this bit of
John you a s20令牌这点
Schottky URI so the two ways you can
肖特基URI，所以您可以通过两种方式
consume Jah tokens one is to provide a
消耗Jah代币之一是提供
key URI and this URI here is I'm just
关键URI，这里只是我的URI
going to throw this in the browser to
打算把它放在浏览器中
show you this spits out an RSA public
向您展示这会吐出RSA公开
key and this public key is used for
密钥，此公钥用于
token verification so on application
令牌验证等应用
startup it's going to hit send point get
启动它将达到发送点获取
that public key and then use that public
该公钥，然后使用该公钥
key for for very after so we set we have
对于非常关键的，所以我们设置了
to do some setup in ua as well so here i
还要在UA中进行一些设置，所以在这里我
think i went over this this initial
认为我已经过了这个最初的
stuff but the initial setup with you a a
的东西，但与您的初始设置
we had to specify the public key which
我们必须指定公钥
is the same show you on that so kinky
是一样的节目，你在那变态
end points but signing keep matching our
终点，但签名保持与我们的匹配
thick private key that's used to Jenna
珍娜曾经用过的厚私钥
and this is the cub isn't like a secret
这是幼崽不是一个秘密
up pipes strength I am participate token
管道强度我参与令牌
encode grant
编码授权
lock it down and it's actually part of
锁定它，它实际上是
the spec is that different grant types
规范是不同的赠款类型
have different levels of security some
具有不同的安全级别
are more kids more secure than others
比其他人更安全的孩子
and over here I'm saying that the
在这里我是说
clients can only authorize this scope so
客户只能授权此范围，因此
the client can only authorize access
客户端只能授权访问
users identity and the authorities field
用户身份和权限字段
here this says what the client own and
这里说客户拥有什么
in UA a this scope UA a dot resource
在UA中，此范围UA是点资源
means that it can access the public key
表示它可以访问公钥
if or no sorry it can access that token
对不起，它可以访问该令牌
key endpoint if that token key endpoint
关键端点（如果该令牌关键端点）
has been secured it can also access the
已被保护，它也可以访问
check token endpoint and do things that
检查令牌端点并执行以下操作
you a allows resource service to do and
您允许资源服务执行和
finally a redirect URI this is important
最后一个重定向URI，这很重要
because this redirect URI locks down how
因为此重定向URI锁定了如何
this client can redirect the user back
该客户端可以将用户重定向回
to the application because remember in
到应用程序，因为记住
that opeth authorization code handshake
授权代码握手
that a one use code gets redirected gets
一个使用代码被重定向得到
sent back to the browser and that is
发送回浏览器，那就是
contained in a redirect so if the
包含在重定向中，因此如果
browser let's say if you had an open
浏览器，如果您打开了
redirect you weren't specifying your
重定向您没有指定您的
redirect URI and in the authorization
重定向URI和授权
request you can say Oh redirect me to
要求您可以说哦，将我重定向到
this bad site if you don't specify a
如果您未指定
redirect URI that's okay the bad site
重定向可以正常运行的URI的站点
will end up getting that authorization
最终将获得该授权
code and then getting the token instead
代码，然后获取令牌
of the site that the token was meant for
该令牌所针对的网站的
so it's really important to specify a
因此，指定一个
redirect URI
重定向URI
and what dependencies did we add to make
以及我们添加了哪些依赖项
this happen
发生这种情况
spring cloud starter oauth2 that's
Spring Cloud Starter Oauth2是
that's it just that one thing okay and
只是一件事还可以，
so let's run it going to restart you AAA
所以我们运行它以重新启动AAA
because I think I changed some config
因为我想我改变了一些配置
there now I'm making changes to you AAA
现在我正在对您进行AAA更改
using this config file but you can also
使用此配置文件，但您也可以
use the UA a CLI it's called you AAC it
使用UA的CLI称其为AAC
is a ruby CLI so if you like ruby then
是一个ruby CLI，所以如果您喜欢ruby
you can just gem install cfd you a AC or
您可以只用gem安装cfd即可使用AC或
there's other ways to install it as well
还有其他安装方法
and okay let's rerun the customer portal
好吧，让我们重新运行客户门户
cool so I try to hit the home page I'm
很酷，所以我尝试访问我的主页
redirected to login screen
重定向到登录屏幕
okay and now I can be the menu I can see
好吧，现在我可以看到菜单了
my access token good all right on to the
我的访问令牌很好，请继续
next and I'll lose all of my nice commit
接下来，我将失去所有的承诺
messages
讯息
all right so I'm going to go over
好吧，我要过去了
testing because testing is super
测试，因为测试是超级
important when you're trying to
当您尝试
configure security on your application
在您的应用程序上配置安全性
you might think that you're doing things
你可能以为你在做事
right and you might be thinking that
是的，您可能会认为
you're following the documentation
您正在遵循文档
exactly as it says but you could miss
确切地说，但您可能会错过
something you could be opening up a big
你可能会打开一个很大的东西
gaping hole in your security so you
安全漏洞
really have to test your application
真的必须测试您的应用程序
thoroughly to make sure that you've
彻底确保您已经
you've done things properly so I'm going
你做得很好，所以我要去
to show you how to do that
告诉你怎么做
now if you're using straight spring
现在，如果您使用直弹簧
security there are some great testing
安全性有一些很棒的测试
tools that have been released somewhat
已经发布的工具
recently that allow you to like mock out
最近，让您喜欢模拟
and authentication and still do like
和身份验证，仍然喜欢
full integration testing but lock
完全集成测试但已锁定
certain things out with spring security
弹簧安全性可以解决某些问题
oauth2 it's I couldn't find the same
oauth2这是我找不到相同的
so I've added a base test class here
所以我在这里添加了基础测试类
security integration test and if you're
安全集成测试，如果您
familiar with testing spring boot
熟悉测试 spring boot
applications this is using that at web
在网络上使用的应用程序
integration test this means that the
集成测试意味着
entire application is starting up it's
整个应用程序正在启动
starting up in a container that's
在一个容器中启动
accessible I'm telling it to start up
可访问性，我告诉它启动
using some random port and I've added a
使用一些随机端口，我添加了一个
bunch of methods here which I guess I'll
一堆方法，我猜我会
go over briefly which allow you to make
简要回顾一下，让您
things that look like HTTP and HTTPS
看起来像HTTP和HTTPS的东西
requests and check the responses on this
请求并检查对此的响应
I could have used could have used rest
我本来可以用休息
template to make requests on the server
在服务器上发出请求的模板
but with rest template I found it
但是用剩下的模板我找到了
difficult to tell it not to follow
很难说不遵循
redirects so what I'm using here to make
重定向，以便我在这里使用
to do these integration tests is apache
做这些集成测试是apache
httpclient and i'm just disabling cookie
httpclient，我只是禁用cookie
management redirects handling so I can
管理重定向处理，以便我可以
use this now to test out a resource
现在使用它来测试资源
server and my customer app
服务器和我的客户应用程序
okay so over here I'm saying that for
好的，所以在这里我是说
this test security dot require SSL
此测试安全点需要SSL
equals true when I'm running in
当我跑步时等于true
production I always want to be running
生产我一直想运行
under SSL but if I'm running under SSL I
在SSL下运行，但是如果我在SSL下运行
want to make sure that that the
想要确保
redirects are properly follow that the
重定向正确遵循
request is being checked if that request
是否正在检查该请求
is over a secure channel is not over a
是通过安全通道而不是通过
secure channel I should expect to see a
安全通道，我应该期望看到
redirect back to the HTTPS URL
重定向回HTTPS URL
and these tests fail let's just dig into
这些测试失败了，让我们深入探讨
this this base method a little bit more
这个基本方法多一点
check requires a GPS no author passing a
检查要求GPS没有作者通过
URI this is calling check HTTP redirect
调用检查HTTP重定向的URI
so I'm going to make an HTTP request and
所以我要发出一个HTTP请求，
on this URI and then look at the
在这个URI上，然后查看
response I am going to expect to get a
回应，我期望得到一个
302 back to HTTPS but that's not
302回到HTTPS，但这不是
happening okay so I expected to be
发生的很好，所以我希望是
redirected to HBS locals menu but I'm
重定向到HBS当地人菜单，但我
redirected to they should be login
重定向到他们应该登录
that's not right how come let's go the
这是不对的，让我们走吧
next
下一个
okay so in this commit I'm going to fix
好的，所以在此提交中，我将修复
the SSL redirection problem this is what
SSL重定向问题，这是什么
was missing
失踪
so when you are using enable off to SSO
因此，当您对SSO使用启用关闭功能时
and you want to force SSL which is
而您想强制使用SSL
always a good idea you do need an oauth2
总是一个好主意，您确实需要一个oauth2
SSO configure adapter this is in the
SSO配置适配器位于
spring cloud security Doc's as a way to
Spring Cloud Security Docs作为一种方式
specify which requests should be secured
指定应该确保哪些请求
with enable oauth2 SSO and if you want
与启用oauth2 SSO，如果需要
to authorize that request if the user
如果用户授权该请求
supposed to contain any roles that sort
应该包含任何排序的角色
of thing you do that all with this
你要做的一切
configure adapter and so out of the box
开箱即用配置适配器
like the last time I ran the application
就像我上次运行该应用程序一样
sure it was asking for authentication
确保它正在要求认证
but I do need to modify that behavior
但我确实需要修改该行为
slightly here and say that over here
在这里稍微说一下
if require SSL is true in my security
如果需要SSL在我的安全中为真
properties then I set this up on the HP
属性，然后在HP上进行设置
security configure it's everyone
安全配置，每个人都可以
familiar with spring security raise
熟悉春季安全提高
hands awesome
真棒
also this is a pattern that's pretty
这也是一个很漂亮的模式
pretty common to spring security setup
在春季安全设置中很常见
okay so now with that I will rerun tests
好吧，现在我将重新运行测试
Green all right let's move on
绿色好吧，继续前进
now we get to create a resource server
现在我们可以创建一个资源服务器
using Springs a data rest and spring
使用Springs数据休息和春天
data JPA it's going back to our diagram
数据JPA，这要回到我们的图表中
yet we did the single sign-on now we're
但是我们现在进行了单点登录
adding the REST API um so this is plain
添加REST API，所以很简单
vanilla and no security okay I've got a
香草，没有安全感，我有一个
manual repository I want to show the IDS
我要显示IDS的手动存储库
on this rest repository and I'm
在这个其余的存储库上，我是
bootstrapping the application with with
使用以下命令引导应用程序
just an object there and what I added to
只是一个对象，还有我添加到的对象
the menu item class is just some GPA
菜单项类别只是一些GPA
annotations because I'm persisting this
注释，因为我坚持这一点
and just go over this briefly some more
然后再简要介绍一下
spring data goodness to get this all
春天的数据善良得到这一切
working you need spring boots started at
工作需要 spring boot 开始
arrests spring boots started a two JPA
逮捕 spring boot 启动了两个JPA
and an in-memory database and fig oh
还有一个内存数据库和图哦
that's it just run on 80 83 I'll be
就是在80 83上运行，我会
running the tests let's run the right
运行测试，让我们运行正确
thing here
这里的东西
okay menu application
好的菜单应用程序
you
您
oh it's asking for basic off now you're
哦，现在要求基本休假
getting get basic auth out of the box if
开箱即用即可获取基本身份验证
you have spring security running in your
您的弹簧安全性正在运行中
application and to turn that off I think
应用程序并关闭它我想
I'm doing that in another commit
我正在另一次提交中
oh yeah here we go security about basic
哦，是的，我们在这里介绍基本信息
naval D equals false and we want to
海军D等于假，我们想
switch basic security off and off and
关闭基本安全功能，然后关闭
use OAuth 2 resource server security
使用OAuth 2资源服务器安全性
okay so what changed
好吧，什么改变了
so to configure resource service
以便配置资源服务
security the resource server it this
保护资源服务器
particular one doesn't need to be
特别是一个不需要
represented by a client in UAA I mean
由UAA中的客户代表
door the same is true if you're not
如果你不这样做，门也是一样
using UAE for a resource server all the
使用阿联酋的资源服务器
resource server needs to do is check the
资源服务器需要做的就是检查
token and verify the signature so you're
令牌并验证签名，以便您
letting it do that by specifying the
通过指定
Jockey URI and changes to the
赛马URI并更改为
application we've added this one
应用程序，我们已经添加了这个
annotation here enable oauth2 resource
此处的注释启用oauth2资源
and we need to add a resource server
我们需要添加资源服务器
configure adaptor again same sort of
再次配置适配器
deal here we want to say that if require
在这里交易，我们想说，如果需要
SSL is true then we want to configure
SSL为真，那么我们要配置
that in each to be security
保证每个人的安全
configuration
组态
and now I'm going to in each subsequent
现在我将在以后的每一个
commit write tests for every change in
提交针对每个更改的写测试
behavior so I'm going to extend security
行为，所以我将扩展安全性
integration test do the same thing here
集成测试在这里做同样的事情
require us a cell to mimic what I want
需要我们一个细胞来模仿我想要的
to do in production we're going to check
在生产中我们要检查
that HTTP GET HTTP redirect when you hit
当您点击时，该HTTP GET HTTP重定向
menu items and then when you hit menu
菜单项，然后单击菜单时
items over HTTP with let's say no token
HTTP上的项目，假设没有令牌
you get a 401 and when you do have a
你得到一个401，当你有一个
token you get a 200 so what's this you a
令牌你得到200，这是什么你
jot token builder it's another class
记记令牌生成器，这是另一类
that I wrote to support all of this
我写来支持所有这些
testing that maybe soon we'll make it
测试也许很快我们就会成功
into a library that you can easily get
进入您可以轻松获得的图书馆
ahold of but it's all in github if you
保留，但是如果您有的话，全部在github中
want to use it today okay let's run the
想今天使用它，好的，让我们运行
tests
测试
it
它
now you might have seen that the test
现在您可能已经看到测试
was not not really adding anything to
并不是真的没有添加任何东西
the token I'm creating a token and it's
我正在创建令牌的令牌，它是
essentially empty token says nothing
本质上为空的令牌什么也没说
doesn't say who the user is doesn't say
不说用户是谁不说
what the audience of the token is you
令牌的受众是什么
don't get any of that so this is
什么都不知道，所以这是
something that obviously we should check
显然我们应该检查的东西
for so to do that
为此
I've added this to resource server
我已将此添加到资源服务器
configure adapter resources resource ID
配置适配器资源资源标识
menu this is something that you you get
菜单，这是你得到的东西
out of the box if you're setting up an
开箱即用，如果您要设置
application with at enable law to
与启用法律一起申请
resource and you say and you add this to
资源，然后您说并添加到
your configuration where is it
您的配置在哪里
yeah you can go spring dotto to resource
是的，您可以将dotto变成资源
ID and with no other configuration here
ID，此处没有其他配置
you know let's say you don't have let's
你知道我们说你没有我们
say you don't have the resource server
说你没有资源服务器
configure adapter you just added that
配置刚添加的适配器
property then your resource then the
属性，然后是您的资源，然后
audience claim would be checked but I
听众的主张将被检查，但我
have to do this manually here and
必须在这里手动执行此操作
through what might be a bug or maybe I'm
通过可能是一个错误或也许我是
not setting things up right if you want
如果您想要的话，不正确的设置
to specify a resource server configure
指定资源服务器配置
adapter you have to do it in a bean that
适配器，您必须在一个
has this signature public resource
有此签名公共资源
server configure a resource server not
服务器没有配置资源服务器
too sure why that is happening but
太确定为什么会这样，但是
that's what I found out through testing
那是我通过测试发现的
that's why testing is so important I
这就是为什么测试如此重要的原因
thought I was doing the right thing and
以为我做对了，
my test failed and I had to figure out
我的测试失败了，我不得不弄清楚
how to make them pass so this test
如何使他们通过考试
here it expects a 403 if I just build a
在这里，如果我只是建立一个403
token that's empty but then if I set the
令牌为空，但是如果我设置了
audience claim on the token as menu then
观众将令牌声明为菜单，然后
it's going to get a 200 feel free to
这将使200随意
interrupt me at all as well
也会打扰我
Oh fail oh okay why expression URL
哦失败哦，好吧，为什么表达式URL
authorization figure already built on
授权图已建立
this table oh I think maybe I'm fixing
这张桌子哦，我想也许我正在修理
this another commit this is not
这另一个承诺这不是
something that I expected so maybe I
我期望的东西，也许我
have to do a little more grooving all
必须多做一些切槽
right let's continue
对，让我们继续
okay and sure menu dot read scope is
好的，确定菜单点的读取范围是
required to access endpoints so adding
需要访问端点，因此添加
some more testing here and some more
这里还有更多测试
authorization
授权书
so now here we're checking for scope and
所以现在我们在这里检查范围和
this is where I was running into that
这就是我遇到的地方
that problem with this method signature
这个方法签名的问题
here being so important I was not able
这里是如此重要，我无法
to get this authorized requests work so
使此授权请求起作用
when you at enable off to resource
当您启用资源时
server or I'm able off to resource you
服务器，或者我可以向您提供资源
get a security expression you get
得到一个安全表达式
security expression methods that allow
允许的安全性表达方法
you to check your token for scopes and
您检查令牌以了解范围和
so the expression here is a lot to have
所以这里的表达有很多
scope menu read so that is saying that
范围菜单已读，也就是说
any request must have the scope in order
任何请求必须具有范围
to proceed and to test for that
进行测试
so it's not enough just to set the
因此仅设置
audience claim I have to set menu dot
观众声称我必须设置菜单点
read or menu dot read has to be present
读取或菜单点读取必须存在
in the token scopes and I wonder if my
在令牌范围内，我想知道我的
tests will pass now
测试将通过
yes
是
okay now I'm using a spring date arrest
好吧，现在我正在使用春季逮捕
in spring data JPA which will just
在 spring data JPA中，
expose JPA repository
公开JPA信息库
restfully so it lets you get stuff from
轻松地让您从中获取东西
it and it also allows you to put and
它，它还允许您放置和
post and delete stuff on it and I want
发布并删除相关内容，我想要
to make sure that those methods are
确保这些方法是
secured with a different scope so this
确保具有不同的范围，因此
is what I'm doing here
这就是我在这里做的
so see the difference here instead of
所以在这里看到区别而不是
using any request I'm using ant matters
使用我使用蚂蚁的任何要求
which lets you specify what request
它可以让您指定什么请求
method you want to apply an access
您要应用访问权限的方法
decision to and so forget we've got menu
决定，所以忘了我们有菜单
dot read but for post put and delete we
点读，但张贴和删除我们
want menu dot right
想要菜单点右
and here you can see our test getting a
在这里您可以看到我们的测试获得了
whole lot longer and we'll go over all
整个更长的时间，我们将遍历所有
that but basically as you add as you
那基本上是你添加的
keep adding security configuration you
继续添加安全配置
need to test thoroughly to make sure
需要彻底测试以确保
that that configuration is doing what
该配置正在做什么
you expect it to do
你期望它能做到
alright let's actually see this work I'm
好吧，让我们实际看看我的工作
going to set up Frank to have menu dot
设置弗兰克有菜单点
read access and that scope will be
读取访问权限，该范围将是
requested in the OAuth authorized
在授权的OAuth中请求
request UA
请求UA
okay so a couple things to set up on you
好的，所以要在您身上设置几件事
a a now I don't expect you guys to be
现在我不希望你们会
using you a you can use your own Olaf to
您可以使用自己的Olaf来
or open ID connect authorization server
或开放ID连接授权服务器
there's my tour project that also has an
我的旅游项目也有一个
open ID connect server but I'm just
打开ID连接服务器，但我只是
using ua a here because I'm very
在这里使用ua a是因为我非常
familiar with it so we added yes
熟悉它，所以我们添加了
ah yes yep sure
嗯是的当然
so you AAA supports Postgres in my
所以您的AAA在我的支持Postgres
sequel oh oh sure so the question was
续集哦，哦，可以肯定的是，这个问题是
how do I configure my data sources in
我如何在
UAA and how do I configure identity
UAA以及如何配置身份
providers in ua let's say if I want to
UA中的提供者，如果我想
hook it up to LDAP or sam'l so yes all
将其连接到LDAP或sam'l，所以全部
of that is possible you can hook it up
这是可能的，你可以把它挂起来
to an external identity provider over
到外部身份提供商
LDAP in sam'l multi-tenancy support is
sam'l多租户支持中的LDAP是
only only allows for sam'l at the moment
目前仅允许萨姆
but we will have multi-tenant LDAP soon
但是我们很快就会有多租户LDAP
for the data sources
用于数据源
it supports Postgres in my sequel all of
它在我的续集中都支持Postgres
this is configurable in you a mo the
这是您可以配置的
your yeah Mahalo can get quite large and
你是的Mahalo可以变得很大
it is quite large in a Cloud Foundry
在Cloud Foundry中相当大
installation but this is all in
安装，但这一切都在
documentation as well if you go to
文档，如果你去
github slash Cloud Foundry Sashi UAA
github斜线Cloud Foundry Sashi UAA
all the documentation is there for that
所有文档都在那里
you can also hit up the mailing list
您也可以点击邮件列表
it's on the captive
在被俘虏
yes so utilities for registering the
是的，所以注册实用程序
application I mean there's a very
应用程序，我的意思是有一个非常
extensive REST API that you can use to
广泛使用的REST API
create off clients and make
创造客户并创造
modifications create users create user
修改创建用户创建用户
groups which are like roles I could have
像我本来可以扮演的角色的小组
and there's also a CLI so you a see that
还有一个CLI，所以您会看到
CLI that I mentioned earlier you can use
我之前提到的CLI可以使用
the CLI to do all these things - I'm not
CLI做所有这些事情-我不是
using the CLI in this demo because it
在此演示中使用CLI，因为它
would just take me too long and I'll
只会花我太多时间，我会
probably make mistakes writing it out so
写出来可能会犯错误
I'm just sort of changing the bootstrap
我只是在改变引导程序
configuration restarting the server so
配置重新启动服务器，以便
that's all in the open source and if
一切都在开源中，如果
you're using pivotal Cloud Foundry then
您正在使用关键的Cloud Foundry
you get a fancy UI well if you're using
如果您使用的是一个很好的用户界面
a multi-tenancy at least show you
多租户至少向您展示
quickly yeah you've got this UI here
很快，是的，您在这里有了这个用户界面
that
那
like I could set the the user store that
就像我可以将用户存储设置为
was that this client is configured to
该客户端配置为
use and redirect your eyes and scopes
使用并重定向您的眼睛和范围
and all that stuff okay
一切都好
does that answer your question great any
那能回答您的问题吗？
other questions
其他问题
yeah
是的
yeah so the question was is there any
是的，所以问题是
way to dynamically change the Scopes
动态更改范围的方法
that are allowed in a token at runtime
在运行时令牌中允许的
of course there is yeah you would do
当然有，你会做
that by let's say let's say this
可以这样说
customer portal you wanted to remove the
您想要删除的客户门户
ability for users that are logging into
登录用户的能力
the customer portal to read menus you
客户门户网站来读取菜单
can do this at runtime just in you a
可以在您自己的时候在运行时执行此操作
just by calling the oauth clients end
只需通过调用oauth客户端即可
point with an ID of customer portal you
用客户门户的ID指向您
do a put and you change the Scopes that
做一个看跌期权，你改变范围
the client is registered to give out if
客户注册后给出
you do this while the server is running
您在服务器运行时执行此操作
and let's say there are tokens that are
假设有一些令牌是
out there being used those tokens will
这些令牌将被使用
still contain that scope but when that
仍然包含那个范围，但是当那个
token expires then you have to get a new
令牌过期，那么您必须获得一个新
token and that token will no longer
令牌，该令牌将不再
contain that scope thanks for the
包含该范围，谢谢
questions it lets me have a little break
问题让我休息一下
showing you all this code but and I
向您展示所有这些代码，但我
can't get through I don't think I'll
无法通过我不认为我会
have enough time to get through the
有足够的时间来度过
entire demo but please if you want to
整个演示，但如果您想
try this out locally just check out the
在本地尝试一下，只需查看
repo and step through every commit and
回购并逐步执行每个提交，
and run it on your own machine it should
并在您自己的机器上运行它
all work okay so where were we
一切正常，所以我们在哪里
we are yeah so we need to into in order
我们是的，所以我们需要进入
to enable menu dot read scope in the
启用菜单点读取范围
customer app we have to ask for that
客户应用程序，我们必须要
scope in the authorized request and so
授权请求中的范围等
that's being done here in application
这是在应用程序中完成的
yeah Mille I've added the scope menu dot
是的Mille我已经添加了范围菜单点
read to the client configuration and
阅读客户端配置并
I've registered register that scope in
我已经在该范围内注册了该范围
UA a for customer portal and I've added
UA a客户门户网站，我已添加
a new user called Frank who will be part
一个名为Frank的新用户，他将加入
of the menu dot read group so I think
菜单点读取组的一部分，所以我认为
about user groups in UA a and clients is
关于UA a和客户端中的用户组是
that
那
you have to go through a client to get a
你必须通过一个客户来获得
token and the Scopes that your token can
令牌以及令牌可以使用的范围
contain is the intersection of this
包含是这个的交集
value here these scopes and the scopes
在这里重视这些范围和范围
are and the groups that the user is a
是和用户是一个组
part of so Frank could have menu dot
的一部分，所以弗兰克可以有菜单点
right as well but when Frank goes
也是正确的，但是当弗兰克去时
through the customer portal his token is
通过客户门户，他的令牌是
only going to have open ID and magnet
只会有开放的ID和磁铁
Reed
芦苇
okay now with this setup let's run
好的，现在通过此设置运行
through it
通过它
oops tore the wrong server
哎呀撕毁了错误的服务器
and I'm going to restart the customer
然后我要重新启动客户
portal and the menu service
门户网站和菜单服务
okay I'm going to well Guinness Frank oh
好吧，我会去健力士弗兰克的哦
cool oh no no no this is this is all
酷哦，不，不，不，这就是全部
running in PWS this is not the one I
在PWS中运行这不是我的那个
want to use use the local one here
想在这里使用本地的
that's the finished product okay um I
那是成品，好吧，我
have to authorize this new scope when
必须在以下情况下授权此新范围
you don't read so now I can them you the
你不读书所以现在我可以给你
menu and this menu still that hard-coded
菜单，此菜单仍然是硬编码的
stuff so I will quickly go through how
的东西，所以我会很快通过
to access a resource server from the SSO
从SSO访问资源服务器
application
应用
okay so in this commit I'm going to set
好的，所以在这次提交中，我将设置
up the hideo's consumption and consume
增加英勇的消费和消费
it using oauth2 rest template the all to
它使用oauth2 rest模板全部
rest template is going to make requests
其余模板将发出请求
to the resource server
到资源服务器
it's going to automatically add the
它会自动添加
users token to that request and that
用户对该请求的令牌，以及
token was stored in session so remember
令牌存储在会话中，因此请记住
that whole authorization codes dance
整个授权码跳舞
that that I showed in my slides all of
我在幻灯片中展示的所有
that is already being done for you and
已经为您完成了，
it's super easy to set up
设置起来超级容易
so I just had to add spring boots
所以我只需要增加 spring boot
started hideous to customer app and
开始对客户应用程序有害
here's what changed I needed to do some
这是我需要做一些改变的地方
configuration so that the all to rest
配置，使所有休息
template can can consume hideous stuff
模板可以消耗可怕的东西
here not sure if I still have to do that
在这里不确定我是否仍然必须这样做
with the latest version okay so now I'm
可以使用最新版本，所以现在
actually making the request for menu
实际提出菜单要求
items and compare this before this is
项目，并在此之前进行比较
hard-coded now I'm using all to rest
硬编码的我现在都在休息
template and all to rest template it's
模板和所有休息模板
just a rest template but in the
只是一个休息模板，但在
background it adds the choke into the
背景将扼流圈添加到
request and let's run it
请求并运行它
oops a round
哎呀一轮
okay nope wrong one there we go
好吧，不，不对，我们走了
the menu great now we can see this is
菜单很棒，现在我们可以看到
real stuff from that menu resource
该菜单资源中的真实内容
server just using that bootstrapped
仅使用该引导程序的服务器
information so we finally were able to
信息，所以我们终于能够
make a connection yep created Frank and
是的，是的，因此建立了联系
now it's accessing the REST API sorry
现在它正在访问REST API
we're a bit out of time I didn't
我们没时间了
actually expect to get through
真正期望通过
everything but in case I was going real
一切，但如果我要真实
quick this is all the stuff every step
快速，这是每一步的全部内容
of the way that happens in order to
为了发生的方式
create value Freddy's barbecue joint
创造价值弗雷迪的烧烤店
again you can follow along a github
再次，你可以按照一个github
please send me comments ask me about all
请给我评论，问我所有问题
the commits that I made and why I did
我所做的承诺以及为什么要做
them and we can continue this connection
他们，我们可以继续这种联系
here
这里
I see questions but we are done I have
我看到了问题，但是我们已经完成了
to give a shout out to the cloud foundry
向云铸造厂大声疾呼
identity team these guys are awesome to
身份团队，这些家伙很棒
work with majora chrisphillip
与Majora chrisphillip合作
Robin Shree and thank you all for coming
罗宾·史瑞（Robin Shree），谢谢大家的光临
to my talk yeah thanks
我的讲话是的，谢谢
okay question time we've got a few
好吧，提问时间，我们有几个
minutes I'm sorry which side oh yeah
分钟，对不起，哪一边哦
yeah for sure yeah write it down cool
是的，肯定的，是的，写下来很酷
also feel free to oh yeah yeah sure
也可以随意哦，是的，肯定的
is that yes yes so as you go through
是的，是的，所以当你经历
these commits you're going to get to a
这些提交，您将获得一个
point where we have all these services
指向我们提供所有这些服务的地方
and I'm just using all these localhost
而我只是使用所有这些本地主机
URLs hard-coded it's a big pain in the
网址经过硬编码，这是
butt if you then add Eureka then you're
如果您再添加尤里卡，那么您就是
off to rest template we'll know we'll
休息模板，我们会知道
use the ribbon clients and do all that
使用功能区客户端并执行所有操作
stuff - yes it's great
东西-是的，很好
yeah sure so scopes on the resource
是的，请确保资源范围
server let's go to the finished product
服务器让我们进入成品
here
这里
okay so this is the menu resource server
好的，这是菜单资源服务器
and we can look at the order application
我们可以看看订单申请
we can't get around to that but and this
我们无法解决这个问题，但是这个
is a little more simple you just say any
简单一点，你只说什么
one you have to have order order dot
一个你必须有订单点
admin to access this order's endpoint
管理员访问此订单的端点
but you can also use method security so
但您也可以使用方法安全性
I've added a pre-authorized annotation
我添加了预先授权的注释
so you can use method security
这样就可以使用方法安全性
annotations and putting your expressions
注释和表达
that way yep
这样呀
yes the question was if somebody gets a
是的，问题是有人是否
hold of my JWT token that I'm pretty
我漂亮的JWT令牌的持有
much exposed yes that is true because it
暴露很多是的，这是真的，因为它
is a bearer token which means if you
是不记名令牌，表示如果您
have that token you are what that token
有那个令牌，你就是那个令牌
says yep
是的
so in this particular example how do you
所以在这个特定的例子中，你如何
protect your token in this example here
在此示例中保护您的令牌
the token actually never leaves the
代币实际上从未离开过
customer you I the token the stored in
客户您我将令牌存储在
session and and then just a session is
会话，然后只有一个会话是
established between the customer UI and
在用户界面和
Frank's browser and so you just have a
弗兰克的浏览器，所以您只有一个
regular session cookie over HTTP and
通过HTTP和
you're good to go if you have to send
如果您必须发送，那很好
that token out you can still send it out
该令牌发出，您仍然可以将其发送出去
to the browser but you really need to
浏览器，但您确实需要
make sure that it's over HTTPS what you
确保通过HTTPS进行验证
can do is also you can encrypt the token
可以做的还可以加密令牌
so if that's how it can contain
所以这就是它可以包含的方式
sensitive information that maybe maybe
敏感信息，也许
you won't even want Frank to be able to
你甚至都不希望弗兰克能够
use that jaat decoder and see what his
使用那个Jaat解码器，看看他的
token contains you can use you can
令牌包含您可以使用的
encrypt it there's a standard called gwe
加密它有一个叫做gwe的标准
that was just finalized there's no
刚刚完成，没有
support for that yet in spring but
在春天还支持
actually if you go through my commits I
实际上，如果您完成我的承诺，我
show you how to use Zul to encrypt
向您展示如何使用Zul进行加密
tokens and so you've got this nice
令牌，所以你有这个好
little gateway to do that cool umm yeah
做这个很酷的小门户嗯是的
thanks for coming if you have any more
多谢您的光临
questions just come up to me I'll sir
问题就问我，先生
yep
是的
so what Zul can do automatically is do
所以祖尔可以自动做的是
the token relay stuff there's
令牌中继的东西
documentation and spring cloud security
文档和Spring Cloud安全性
for that but I don't really go into that
为此，但我不是很喜欢
in my example my example of Howell is
在我的示例中，我的Howell示例是
used is really just for that token
真的只是用于该令牌
encrypt decrypt
加密解密
you
您